{
    "id": "16ed5e8f978240e4889780ec9c3b2d27",
    "title": "Sentence Completion Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Let’s watch a movie, ……………………?",
            "description": "Shall we is used in question tags after let's.",
            "answers": [
                "can we",
                "shall we",
                "should we"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "None of the students participated in the program, ……………………….?",
            "description": "Affirmative tags are used after negative expressions like none, hardly, seldom etc. ",
            "answers": [
                "did they",
                "didn't they",
                "had they"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I bought a laptop. Change voice.",
            "description": "In the simple past, the passive form is made with was/were + v3.",
            "answers": [
                "A laptop is bought by me.",
                "A laptop was bought by me.",
                "A laptop has been bought by me."
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She was cooking dinner. Change voice.",
            "description": "In the past continuous, the passive form is made with was/were + being + v3.",
            "answers": [
                "Dinner was cooking her.",
                "Dinner was cooked by her.",
                "Dinner was being cooked by her."
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "She said to me, ‘I have lost faith in you.’ Change into indirect speech.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "She told me she has lost faith in me.",
                "She told me that she lost faith in me.",
                "She told me that she had lost faith in me."
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "If I hadn’t overslept, I …………………….. the train.",
            "description": "In the third conditional, we use a past perfect tense in the if clause and would + have + past participle in the main clause. ",
            "answers": [
                "wouldn't have missed",
                "wouldn't miss",
                "won't miss"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Haste ……………………. waste.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "creates",
                "generates",
                "produces",
                "makes"
            ],
            "correct": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "The man along with his children ……………………… walking in the rain.",
            "description": "When we connect two subject with along with, the verb agrees with the first subject. ",
            "answers": [
                "was",
                "were"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Thousand dollars ……………………. not a small sum.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "are",
                "is",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I …………………… the office at",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "left",
                "have left",
                "had left"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "A person who works for somebody in order to learn a skill",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "assistant",
                "freshman",
                "disciple",
                "apprentice"
            ],
            "correct": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "He decided ………………….. the blue shirt.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "for",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        }
    ]
}